嘿,艾玛 你最好现在感谢这个还能支撑你..
Hey,Emma,you better appreciate this while it lasts..
因为当你长大了,你就不能整天都坐着啦!
because when you get older,you're not gonna be able to just sit around all day.
-确实 -是啊
- So true. - Yeah.
-嘿！ -嘿！
- Hey. - Hey.
我们来道别,要去俄亥俄州
We're here to say goodbye. We're off to Ohio.
对呀，你们要去领养面试
Oh,right,your adoption interview.
对方有可能是我们宝宝的妈妈
Yep. We'll meet the lady who could be carrying our baby.
难以置信,你们回家时会带着宝宝!  很奇怪
I can't believe it. When you come back,you'll have a baby. That is so weird.
也很不正确
And so incorrect.
她怀孕没几个月
She's only a couple months pregnant.
她选中了我们的申请表,是否喜欢我们还不一定
She liked our application but might not like us.
她会相中你们的!
Come on,she's gonna love you guys.
谢谢,我们满怀希望
Thank you. But we're trying not to get our hopes up.
看运气吧
A lot could still get in our way.
她可能会决定拒绝把孩子给人领养 也可能选中其他夫妇
She could decide against adoption,like another couple better.
你们打算给小孩取啥名字?
What are you gonna name it?
我就有这个本事，费尽口舌 而旁人却充耳不闻
I could develop a condition in which I talk and talk and no one hears a word.
试想,如果一切顺利
But just think,okay? What if everything goes right?
她真选了你们俩
What if this woman does pick you guys?
天呐!那她就会选我们
Oh,my God. She's gonna pick us!
我们决心，决不轻易放弃希望
So we're standing firm on "not getting our hopes up"?
我明白,有可能出差错,但万一顺利
No. I know things could still go wrong,but if they don't..
我们就会有孩子了 孩子!
if this works out,we're gonna have a baby. A baby!
- 是的，但是… -会成功的!
- Yes. But.. - Oh,my God. It's gonna work!
我们会尽力!
We're gonna make it work!
我要当妈妈,你要当爸爸
I'm gonna be a mommy,and you're gonna be a daddy!
回见了笨蛋,我要去领我的宝宝
All right,I'll see you suckers. I'm gonna go get me a baby!
去你们的,我要当爸啦
Screw it. I'm gonna be a daddy!
代理孕母
The.One.With.The.Birth.Mother
菲比跟谁一起?
Hey,who's Phoebe with?
麦克！
Mike.
不，乔伊 和菲比站在门口的是谁?
No,Joey. Who is Phoebe with at the door?
我想说,会跟我上床的姑娘
I wanna say,"Someone I'm gonna have sex with."
-嘿！ -嘿！
- Hey. - Hey.
-你朋友? -莎拉
- So who's your friend? - Oh,that's Sarah.
不，你少打我朋友的主意！
No. Don't you get any ideas.
我再也不给你撮合我的朋友了
I'm not setting you up with any more of my friends.
- 为什么？为什么？ -你约会人家一次,睡一个
- Why? Why? - Because you'll date her once..
然后就把人家忘到九霄云外
sleep with her,then forget she exists.
举例说明
Name one friend of yours I did that with.
-曼蒂 -曼蒂，是吗？
- Mandy. - Mandy,huh?
金发丰胸辣妹?
Really hot blond,big boobs?
-错 -我明白为什么会忘了她了
- No. - Might be why I don't remember,huh?
你好象把我当别人了?
Do you think I'm someone else?
过去我也许待你朋友不好
Look,I may not have treated your friends well in the past.
但我现在成熟多了,真的,瑞秋
But I have grown up a lot. Really. Honest. Rach?
信不信由你,是真的
Yeah,believe it or not,it's true.
乔伊和我交往的时候很乖
I mean,when Joey and I were together..
体贴,成熟
he was wonderful. He was thoughtful and mature.
我们交往那一周
And for the one week that we went out..
他没和其他女人上床
he didn't sleep with anybody else.
成长
Growth.
-好,给你她的电话号码 -谢谢
- Fine,I'll give you her number. - Okay. Thank you.
我保证这个不会忘记
And I promise you I will not forget this one.
-曼蒂 -莎拉
- Mandy. - Sarah!
莎拉
Sarah.
- 嘿！ - 嗨！
- Hey. - Hi.
- 嗨！ -嗨,给点着装建议
- Hey. - Hey,guys,I need some fashion advice.
帽子好看吗?
How does this look?
有点低了..抬高点,再高,再高,好了
Well,it's.. It's a little low. Pick it up a little.
再高
A little bit more.
好了
There you go.
扔一边去
Now throw it away.
别这样,是好帽子
Come on! This looks good.
信我,我一个月买30本时尚杂志
Ross,please trust me. I buy 30 fashion magazines a month.
我不清楚谁在竞选总统,也不知道北约那家伙是谁
Now I don't know who's running for president or who that NATO guy is..
但我知道,你该离那帽子越远越妙
but I do know that you have to get far away from that hat.
见鬼
Damn it. God..
明晚我要约会,我得扮帅才行
I have this date tomorrow night,and I have to look cool.
-她是谁? -她叫琼
- Well,who's the girl? - Her name's Joan.
她在时尚界工作 她在Hugo Boss（服装品牌）工作
She's in fashion. She works for Hugo Boss.
Hugo Boss?你不是说她在时尚界工作吗?
Hugo Boss? I thought you said she was in fashion.
在罗夫罗兰的办公室说这些 你就死定了
At the Ralph Lauren offices,that would've killed.
如果你需要着装建议 明天我和瑞秋要去购物
If you want fashion help,Rachel and l are going shopping tomorrow.
-欢迎同去 -真的?太好了
- You're welcome to come with us. - Really? That would be great.
我必须有备而去
I mean,I have to do something.
她总是取笑我的衣着
She kind of teased me about how I dress.
显然,就凭你那衬衣
I can see why. Nice shirt.
你和我穿得一样啊
You're wearing the same shirt.
愚蠢的随处都是的GAP（美国最大服装公司）
Stupid Gap on every corner!
随便坐,我带艾瑞卡过来
Make yourselves comfortable,and I'll be back with Erica.
好，谢啦！
Okay,thank you.
总算到了
Well,this is it.
- 你状态如何? -很好,有点奇怪
- Are you okay? - Yeah,it's just weird,you know?
"我叫钱德,你体内的小人 可以给我养吗?"
It's like,"Hi,I'm Chandler. May I have the human growing inside you?"
你会表现出色
You're gonna be great.
你也是
显然
Well,obviously.
莫妮卡,钱德 这位是艾瑞卡
Monica? Chandler? I'd like you to meet Erica.
-嗨！ -真高兴跟你见面
- Hi. - Hi. It is so,so nice to meet you.
-嗨！ -谢谢你同意见我们
- Hi. - Thank you for agreeing to see us.
-嗨！ -你们熟悉一下
- Hi. - I'll let you get acquainted.
- 好的！ -莫妮卡和钱德?
- Okay. - So it's Monica and Chandler?
我只知道你们是“档案CRW33815-D”
I only know you as "File CRW33815-D."
朋友们爱这么叫我们
That's what our friends call us.
你们这一对令人羡慕
Gosh,you know,you're just such an amazing couple. It's..
简直叫人嫉妒
kind of intimidating.
是吗?
I don't know about that.
你在开玩笑吗?我是说，您是医生
Are you kidding me? I mean,it's enough that you're a doctor.
可您竟娶了个牧师!
But on top of it,you're married to a reverend?
-我认为... -让她说完,医生
- I don't think that's exactly.. - Let her finish,doctor.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
- Hey. - Hey.
莎拉昨晚跟你一起很愉快
My friend Sarah had a great time last night.
-是吗 -是啊,这次你会再约她?
- Yeah. - Yeah,so you gonna call this one back?
绝不
No.
什么意思,莎拉很棒
What are you talking about? Sarah's great.
是吗?你知道你的很棒的朋友 干了什么好事?
Oh,really? You want to know what your "great" friend did?
我们出去吃饭
We're out to dinner,okay?
相处融洽,和谐
We were getting along,having a really nice time.
我觉得她很可爱
I was thinking she was really cool.
突然间
And then,out of nowhere..
就这样?
That's it?
这是你不理她的理由?
That's why you won't go out with her again?
吃你的薯条有什么大不了?
So she took some fries. Big deal.
我不是气她吃我几根薯条
Hey,look,it's not about a few fries.
你得清楚薯条的象征意义
It's about what the fries represent.
-什么? -所有食物!!!
- What? - All food!
对不起
Well,I'm sorry.
竟然介绍你和"怪物"约会
I can't believe I set you up with such a monster!
我带女孩吃饭
Hey,look,I take a girl out..
她点什么都可以,多吃无妨
she can order whatever she wants. The more the better,all right?
但不可以自己 只点沙拉却夺我的食物
Just don't order a garden salad and then eat my food!
这么做有可能被切手指的!
That's a good way to lose some fingers.
-谢天谢地你来了,你来听听 -什么?
- Thank God you're here. Listen to this. - What?
乔伊昨晚约会我朋友.晚饭时
Joey and my friend are out last night,having dinner,and she reaches over..
-她伸手拿他的薯条 -不!
- and takes a few of his fries.. - Oh,no!
这有什么?
What?
你知道这条规则?
You know about the plate thing?
我了解乔伊从不分享食物
Oh,yeah,yeah. No,Joey doesn't share food.
上星期我们早餐时
I mean,just last week we were having breakfast..
他盘里有些葡萄
and he had a couple grapes on his plate.
-你不让她吃葡萄? -不是我
- You wouldn't let her have a grape? - No,not me.
是艾玛
Emma.
乔伊从不分享食物!!!
Joey doesn't share food!
我仍然认为因为这条破事就 放弃好女孩很不明智
Well,I still think that is a stupid reason not to call someone again.
你再约她,如果有必要
You are calling her,okay?
干脆再点一盘薯条不就完了?
And if you need to,then just get an extra plate of fries for the table.
我喜欢
I like that.
共享缓冲区
A sharing buffer. Yeah.
多点一盘薯条 再点一盘洋葱
Yeah,I'll order some extra fries. Maybe a plate of onion rings.
好好！
Yeah. Yeah.
还要冷盘虾
And a shrimp cocktail.
和辣鸡翅
And some Buffalo wings.
或许，一份披萨
Maybe.. Maybe an individual pizza,huh?
和牛排
And some mozzarella sticks.
我们在谈什么?
What were we talking about?
哇,这地方真吓人 人人都那么吝啬
Wow,this place is awesome. Everyone is so mean.
太有意思了!
So fun.
我们走吧,我在这寻不到什么的
We should just go. I'm not gonna find anything here.
这的东西都太可笑了
This stuff is ridiculous.
这地方真不赖!
Oh,this place is great!
好了,你们开心吧 我要用这种声音和人聊天了
Okay,you guys have fun. I'm gonna go talk to people in this voice.
拜托,我才不穿银色的
Rach,come on,I'm not gonna wear any of this. Nothing silver.
- 为什么？ - 有毛毛领的
- Why? - Okay,nothing with hair.
更不穿带挂锁的
And nothing with padlocks on it!
我知道有些衣裳不入你眼
Ross,look. Look,I know that some of this stuff is out there.
但你看这件
But I mean,come on,look at this. Look at this sweater.
多美
I mean,this is just beautiful.
是很柔软
Wow,this is really soft.
350元?
Three hundred and fifty dollars?
从700块打折下来!你差不多省了200块!
Down from 700. You're saving,like,200 bucks.
逻辑学和数学都饱受摧残
Both logic and math are taking a serious hit today.
这件好,很衬你
Hey,check this out. It's totally you.
- 哇哦！ - 嗯
- Wow. - Yeah.
哇哦！这件看起来不错。
Wow. Actually,this looks pretty good.
是啊！
Yeah.
"孩子就是孩子"(舞曲名)?
"Boys will be boys"?
-本来就是! -好好。
- What? They will be! - All right.
-算了,我走 -别，罗斯，等等嘛！
- That's it,I'm getting out of here. - No,Ross,wait,come on.
还有其他的呢， 衣裳和裤子都不错
There's other stuff here. There's some nice shirts,these nice pants.
其实，这些看起来挺适合我
Actually,these might look pretty good on me.
嗯，不错。这样,你随便转转先
Yes,they will. You know what you should do? Go take a walk.
我知道你尺码,我帮你挑些上等货色
All right? I know your size,and I'll pick out some really good stuff for you.
-当真? -对
- Really? - Yes.
我知道男人穿什么最性感
I know what looks sexy on guys.
穿我推荐的衣服,不迷死她才怪
Just wear what I suggest,and she is gonna go nuts for you.
你是说…
So you're saying..
我若穿这条裤子，她会允许我侵犯?
if I wear these pants,I might be getting into hers?
为什么男人老跟我来这套?
Why do men keep talking to me like this?
我是医生,我太太是牧师,
So the fact that I'm a doctor and my wife's a reverend..
这对你很重要?
that's important to you?
是啊,很多申请人都很优秀
Yeah. I read some great applications..
但是,带孩子谁也比不上牧师
but I thought,"Who better than a minister to raise a child?"
阿门
Amen.
何况还有医生的妙手
Plus,I thought the baby would be in good hands with a doctor.
很好的一双手。
Good hands.
疗伤圣手
Healing hands.
牧师,圣经上有写领养孩子吗?
Reverend,can I ask? Does the Bible say anything about adoption?
写了:但做无妨!
It says,"Do it."
(模仿圣经句式:)她让他们领养了一个婴孩 (原为"你要怀孕生子，可以给他起名叫耶稣")
"And behold,she did adopt unto them a baby.
此乃善举
And it was good."
-哇 -我也哇
- Wow. - Yeah,wow.
我在想 你们工作都责任重大
I was wondering.. You both have such serious jobs.
有时间照顾宝宝? 还兼顾你的教友们?
Would you have time to take care of a baby and your flock?
- 我的教友？ - 你们教堂里的人。
- My flock? - People in your church.
哦，我的教友。
Oh,my flock.
我的教友? 我的教友们很不错
Oh,no,my flock? My flock is good.
现在他们能照顾自己
Yeah. My flock pretty much takes care of themselves by this point.
很好的教友，教友，教友，教友
Good flock. Flock,flock,flock.
当医生很花时间吧?
But being a doctor,that must take up a lot of time.
我的情况不同
Not for me it doesn't.
谈得如何?
So how's everything going in here?
问题问完了，很满意
We're great. I think I may have asked all my questions.
你们有什么要问她?
Good. Do you have questions for Erica?
我想问问,你读到满意的申请表
Yeah,actually. So you read a file that you liked..
然后告诉代理人编号 然后他们联系到我们?
and then you gave the agency the serial number and they contacted us?
我们的系统中用户完全匿名
Yes. Our system ensures total anonymity.
-我们以此为荣 -应该骄傲
- We're very proud of it. - You should be.
的确是一流
You're really on top of stuff.
别的没什么了?那我们俩谈谈
Well then,if there's nothing else,then the two of us should talk.
实际上…
I actually..
-我想我们不必谈了 - 为什么不？
- I don't think we have to. - We don't?
我看了你们的档案就确定要选你们
Yeah,when I read about you two,I was pretty sure I wanted you..
但还想当面见见你们
but I just thought we should meet face to face.
我决定了
I've made my decision.
就选他们
I choose them.
哦，天啊，太棒了
Oh,my God,this is great.
太棒了，听见吗
This is so great. Did you hear that?
是的，听见了
Yeah,I did.
嘿！
Hey.
谢谢，太谢谢了
Thank you. Thank you so much.
你将来一定进天堂!
You are so going to heaven!
- 我们买了些很棒的东西。 - 对！
- We got some really great stuff. - Yeah.
但是，有些胸罩似乎不妥
Yeah,but I'm not sure about some of the bras I got.
真的?你能穿上试给我看吗？
Really? Do you want to try some of them on for me?
好
Okay.
等一下，我们是在乔伊的幻想里吗?
Wait,are we in Joey's imagination?
糟糕,错拿罗斯一袋
Oh,no. I took one of Ross' bags by mistake.
我那件不见了
And one of mine is missing.
肯定在罗斯那里,找他拿回来好了
Ross probably has it. You'll get it from him later.
如何?
So,what do you think?
这次我们可没穿一样!
I think we're not wearing the same shirt anymore.
对，瑞秋帮我选的
Yeah. Yeah,Rachel picked it out for me.
她让我相信她 真高兴我答应了,一路回头率暴高!
She told me to trust her,and you know what? I'm glad I did.
在来的路上,有很多人看我
I turned quite a few heads on my way over here.
老兄,别穿成这样
Dude,I really don't think you should be wearing that.
我明白
I see.
有人怕我抢走了女人的目光
Somebody's afraid of a little competition with the ladies?
有人好象变成了女人!
Looks like someone is the ladies!
你嫉妒,因为你没出风头
You're just jealous because you couldn't pull this off.
现在失陪了,我约会去
Yeah. Now if you'll excuse me,I have a date.
看到没？大家都只看我!
See? All eyes on me!
-不能签 -为什么?
- We are not signing those papers. - Why not?
这不对,他们搞错,当我们是别人
It's wrong. They made a mistake. They think we're somebody else.
上帝的安排,凡人懂什么
God works in mysterious ways.
别再冒充了!
You have got to stop.
但她喜欢我们
But she liked us.
她喜欢的是钱德医生和莫妮卡牧师
She likes Doctor Chandler and Reverend Monica.
回想一下，我其实满像牧师
If you think about it,I'm kind of like a reverend.
作为厨子,我给饥饿的人和穷人提供食物
I mean,as a chef,I serve God by feeding the hungry and poor.
你一份牛排卖34块9毛5!
Your veal chop is 34.95!
拜托,我认为这是我们的机会
Come on,I just.. I think we've been given an opportunity.
不如将错就错,他们都在签协议了
The mistake's already made. They're writing up the papers now.
但我们是冒充的
But we're not the ones she chose.
你竟然理直气壮
How can you feel okay about this?
因为…
Because.
虽然我们不是她选中的人
We may not be who she thinks we are..
但没人比我们更爱那个小宝宝
but no one will ever love that baby more than us.
- 我明白 - 我的意思是
- I know. - I mean,who knows..
谁知道我们到底还要等多久 才会有人给我们宝宝?
how long it's gonna take for someone else to give us a baby?
万一永远没人选我们?
What if no one ever picks us?
哦，亲爱的
Oh,honey..
行吗？
Please?
求你了，我们快成功了
Please. We are so close.
莫妮卡，我也想要孩子
Monica,I want a baby too.
但她要送出她的孩子
But this woman is giving away her child.
她应该知道对方的真实身份
She deserves to know who it's going to.
好吧，你说的没错
Okay. You're right.
我们跟她坦白,
So we'll tell the truth.
而且谁知道呢,对吧? 没准，她喜欢的是咱俩本人
And who knows,you know? Maybe she'll like us for us.
或许！
Maybe she will.
我怎么就不是牧师呢!
Why couldn't I have been a reverend?
你是犹太人
You're Jewish.
技术性的问题
Technicality!
女士点的戈登沙拉
Garden salad for the lady.
看来很诱人,真会点
Oh,that looks great. Good ordering.
男士点的海鲜拼盘,另有一盘薯条,请慢用
Seafood platter for the gentleman,and extra fries.
请慢用
Enjoy.
薯条很美味
Those fries look delicious.
你也喜欢吃法国薯条?
I didn't know you liked French fries.
吃吧,我的就是你的
Help yourself. What's mine is yours.
好大的清蒸粉蚌
Wow,are those stuffed clams?
对,是我的清蒸粉蚌
Yes,they are my stuffed clams.
吃薯条如何?
How about those fries,though,huh?
-真美味 -是啊
- They are delicious. - Yeah.
你真漂亮，知道吗
You are beautiful,you know that?
你嘴好甜
That is so sweet.
好！
Okay,then.
你捣什么乱!
Now look what you did!
怎么回事?
What? What is the matter with you?
我不喜欢别人抢我的东西吃
I don't like it when people take food off of my plate,okay?
但你说过"我的就是你的"
But you said,"What's mine is yours."
我指的不是这个!
Well,I didn't mean it!
好吧,对不起,没想到你这么在乎
Fine. Sorry,I didn't think it was that big a deal.
抱歉
No,I'm sorry. I..
我反应过激,食物方面
I'm overreacting,okay? It's just,when it comes to food,I..
我有一些戒律
have certain rules..
我是说
okay? I mean..
有些事可以做,有些事严禁做
there are things you do,and,you know,things that you don't do.
这儿很不错
Wow,this place looks great.
你会喜欢的,真高兴我们在一起
Oh,you are gonna love it. And I'm so glad we're finally doing this.
-我也是 -我来
- Me too. - Here.
真有趣！
So this was fun.
刚才的事真抱歉
I really am sorry about,you know,before.
我想说,我真的喜欢你
And I want to make sure you know I really do like you.
是啊,但是没有喜欢蛤蚌那么多
Sure,just not as much as clams.
清蒸粉蚌
Well,stuffed clams..
女士要的巧克力甜品
Chocolate torte for the lady.
男士的奶酪蛋糕
Cheesecake for the gentleman.
抱歉，我的蛋糕上不是应该有些红葡萄吗？
Excuse me,sir. There seems to be some sort of red crap on my cheesecake.
是的，那是覆盆子
Yes,that's a raspberry coulis.
覆盆子不是一种猴子吗?
Coulis is not a monkey?
当我看到覆盆子这个词的时候 我还以为是一种猴子呢！
When I read the description I thought it came with a little raspberry monkey.
- 哦，天啊 - 我要换成她那种
- Oh,my God. - I'll just have what she's having instead.
抱歉先生，那是最后一块了
Oh,I'm sorry,sir. That was our last piece.
点奶酪蛋糕真够蠢,试着保持健康吧
I'm so stupid ordering cheesecake,trying to be healthy.
哦，不
Oh,no.
工作电话,我得复机
This is work. I should call in. Can you excuse me?
请便
Yeah,sure. No problem.
干嘛?你不是不和人分享食物?
What are you doing? I thought you don't share food?
确实是
Sure I do.
要覆盆子吗？
Coulis?
不，我都不能吃你的蛤蚌 你也不能碰我的甜品
No. If I can't have your clams,you can't have my dessert.
规则是双向的
This is a two-way street.
是吗?
Really?
是的。
Really.
我回来时希望它完好无损
Now this all better be here when I come back.
当然,我能控制自己
Yeah,of course. I can control myself.
别再瞪着我!
Stop staring at me!
就一小口
Just a tiny little..
我不说对不起
I'm not even sorry.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
- Hi. - Hey.
领养的初步手续就这些了
So these are the preliminary forms for an open adoption.
后续的手续还很多,希望一切顺利
There's a lot to go over,but I'll explain as we go through.
-孩子的照片? - 对
- Is that a picture? - Yeah.
是上周给宝宝拍的超声波
It's a sonogram they took of the baby last week.
你们也许有兴趣看看
I thought you might want to see it.
医生快看
Look,doctor.
签字前我们得谈谈
Look,before we sign anything,we really have to talk.
我们不是你选中的夫妇
We're not who you think we are.
-什么意思? -代理公司肯定出错了
- I don't understand. - The agency must have made a mistake.
我太太不是牧师,我不是医生
My wife is not a reverend,and I'm not a doctor.
-啊? -不可能
- What? - That's impossible.
我可以替你开刀,向你证明
I could perform an operation on you and prove it if you'd like.
我去查档案，失陪一下
I have to check your file. Excuse me.
你们到底是谁?
So who are you?
我们是叫莫妮卡,钱德,纽约来的
Our names really are Monica and Chandler. We're from New York.
但重要的是
Yeah,but the important thing to know about us..
我们真的很爱这个小孩
is how much we would care for this little baby.
你们先前跟我撒谎?
So you lied to me before?
我们给了假的“证词”
Well,we "bore false witness."
看,我真有当牧师的天赋
See? I could be a reverend.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我们希望说明真相后
But we were hoping that since we told you the truth..
-你能网开一面 -把我的宝宝给你们?
- that you still might consider.. - Giving you my baby?
把孩子给两个骗子?
You think I'd give you my child after this?
不必马上决定，请看看我们的档案
You don't have to decide now. If you look at our file..
没兴趣,到此为止
I don't want to look at your file. This is over.
艾瑞卡 请等等,
Erica,wait.
我跟你无话可说
I have nothing to say to you.
你很有理由生气
Look,you have every reason to be upset.
我们是撒了谎
We did lie.
但那是因为我们想要个孩子等太久了
But only because we've been waiting and trying to have a baby for so long.
我们也不知道下一个机会 何年何月才会到来
And we don't know how long it's gonna be before we get another chance.
让你的牧师祈祷去吧!
Why don't you ask the reverend to pray on it?
艾瑞卡,等等
Erica,please.
考虑一下我们吧 找他们要我们的资料
Just consider us. Ask them to see our file.
我们姓宾
Our last name's Bing.
我太太是厨师，我从事广告业
My wife's a chef,and I'm in advertising.
嗯
Oh,yeah.
我的确喜欢你们
I actually liked you guys.
但你们不该撒谎
But it doesn't matter. What you did was wrong.
但你喜欢我们对不对
But you did like us.
你没有喜欢错
And you should.
我太太很了不起
My wife's an incredible woman.
有爱心,乐于奉献,关怀他人
She is loving,and devoted and caring.
别告诉她我这么说 但是她的确一贯正确
And don't tell her I said this,but the woman's always right.
我爱我太太胜过世上一切事物
I love my wife more than anything in this world.
所以..
And it..
不能给她个孩子,我难受得要命
It kills me that I can't give her a baby.
我很想要孩子
I really want a kid.
有了孩子以后 我会学习如何做个好爸爸
And when that day finally comes,I'll learn how to be a good dad.
但我太太…
But my wife..
她已经做好了准备
she's already there.
她是一个妈妈
She's a mother..
可惜没孩子
without a baby.
求你了
Please?
你还要那孩子吗?
You still want that baby?
上帝保佑钱德宾
God bless you,Chandler Bing!
原来这是女人穿的
Turns out this sweater is made for a woman.
那你还穿?
So why are you still wearing it?
因为它摸起来很软
Because it's soft.
今天过得如何?
Hey,so how was your date?
不太好
Not so good.
看起来今晚就咱俩了是吧老兄
Well,looks like it's just the two of us tonight,huh,buddy?
是啊,你知道吗，我们够倒霉的
Yeah. And you know what? We could do a lot worse.
-是啊 - 嗯
- Yeah. - Yeah.
乔伊从不分享食物!
Joey doesn't share food!